Okay, so now you
have an umbrella statement,
three buyer problems, a
channel, marketing, and offer
audit complete. And you
might not have realized
this, but you are
further ahead than most
creators, even with six
-figure subscriber counts, because
you've got some clarity.
And even if it
seems like everything is
a mess, clarity is
potentially worth millions eventually.
So give yourself a
pat on the back.
You're doing an amazing
job so far. Right,
now what we're gonna
do is we're gonna
work out our 10X,
our 2X, and our
minus 10X tasks based
on this information. So
a 10X task is
one that if you
do it, can have
a 10X result on
your business. So let's
say you have tons
of views and low
sales, the 10X task
now becomes fixing the
sales page and your
offer so that you
can turn more of
those views into sales.
Or if you look
and go, oh my
gosh, my channel and
offer and email are
all out of line.
Well, fixing this is
your 10X task over
the medium term, because
anything else you do
won't have impact unless
it's working. Now a
2X task is a
task that is helpful,
but it doesn't really
progress you much. That's
things like responding to
comments or doing admin
or emailing people that
you really don't have
to. And a minus
10X task is things
like editing, trying to
grow an Instagram account
at the same time
as a YouTube channel,
or working on things
that can be outsourced
really easily. And the
good news is your
10X task right now
is just to do
what our plumber did
after they found the
block in the sink
and that was to
try a quick fix
before they tore the
whole kitchen apart and
gave themselves more work
that maybe could have
been avoided. So to
do that, we're just
going to take some
small actions on any
red sections we found
in your pipeline with
minor adjustments. And then
after that, your 10X
task is to make
new videos to try
and get viewers to
go into your pipeline.
And that will then
start to reveal if
we need to do
anything more major. For
some of you, we
won't, for many of
you, we will. Now,
if you're in a
position where you scored
green on all three,
then just move on
to the next module
right now. So now
I'm going to give
you some data benchmarks
that will help you
work out your next
move. And so if
you looked at your
data and it said,
your sales page was
out of line with
your channel and your
conversion rate is currently
under 1%, what we
want to do is
do some minor adjustments
where we're going to
rewrite the headline on
the page to be
positioned to solve the
problem. You're going to
position yourself as the
expert in solving. Now,
there's a video on
writing headlines and sub
headlines in the advanced
module about offers. You
can watch that to
help guide you here.
And to calculate your
sales page conversions, you
take the amount of
purchases in the last
90 days and divide
by the unique sales
page visitors, then times
that by 100. If
you don't have the
data of your sales
page, then your only
10X task is to
install Google Analytics or
RevTrack so that you
can then get it
over time. This is
critical data we need.
Keep in mind, RevTrack
only tracks link clicks.
So if you have
traffic coming from Google
or other places to
your sales page, you
need to install Google
Analytics. You can search
yourself on how to
do that, but most
landing page builders will
give you that data
anyway. All right, so
do that. Now, if
your email opt -in
page or your lead
magnet opt -in page
got a red flag
and is converting less
than 40 % of
the people who arrive
on it to sign
up, I want you
to watch the video
on writing an email
signup page in the
email module in the
advanced section and change
your headline and sub
headline. Make it speak
directly to the umbrella
problem. And then to
work that out, use
the same calculation. Look
at how many people
went to that page,
how many of them
signed up, and then
times that by 100.
Again, if you don't
have a data, it's
critical. You get it
over time because we
build everything around this
data. And if your
metrics are above any
of those benchmarks, don't
change anything yet. These
are just small, simple
fixes that can sometimes
flip a red light
green. But don't expect
all your problems to
be solved overnight doing
this. It's very likely
we're gonna have to
do more optimization down
the line. All right,
so you're probably filming
very overwhelmed right now.
You're worried your new
positioning might be wrong,
or you might be
thinking, this is so
much. I didn't know
I had to fix
this many things. I
didn't even know these
things existed. That's very
normal. Don't worry. We
have just performed open
heart surgery on your
entire business model. So
you're now capable of
starting your transformation into
the Hulk. Now comes
the recovery, the rebuild.
So once you've made
those minor changes, here's
how we're gonna move
forward. If you don't
have an email nurture
campaign set up, that
is your side mission
to go to next.
An email nurture is
this part of our
system where you build
an email signup form.
And then when they
sign up to it,
you auto email them
with some value and
then some promotion to
try and get them
to convert something. And
for people who don't
have one, we're not
gonna build a big
30 day in campaign.
We're literally just gonna
build a one to
three welcome sequence. Why?
Because without traffic from
your videos, we're just
kind of guessing what
buyers want from you
right now. So there's
no point doing anything
bigger until we learn
more about them posting
videos. If you already
have one, just keep
that. Don't do anything
else. So that's it.
Go and fix any
red lights with minor
tweaks only. And then
move on to phase
two, where we're gonna
make our first little
test video together.